Each week,
I take a bit of time out of my diary to
roast people online with
love. Typically, social media
and their sales process from there within.
I do this for a living.
I help hundreds of businesses.
Today, most of them
are in the fitness industry.
But even if you're not in the fitness
industry,
I'm sure you can still take a lot
from things we're going to talk about.
All of these roasts come from a place of
love, and if you'd like to put your hat in
the ring for one of the next roasts,
you can do so by clicking the link in the
description. And remember,
the only way I could be truly unkind
is not to be honest
with you. So let's begin.
mtirab performance online.
M-T-E-R...
It's just quite difficult to read
that for a start.
Is Max Everard available? I'm not sure.
So from the beginning, from the off,
that as a username
is just quite difficult to
read. Your profile picture
is way underexposed. I can't see you.
You kind of look, no offense,
a bit pedo-ish, like a nonce hiding in the
shadows. Hello, children. Let's dial
that exposure up a bit because it looks
like
a potentially professionally taken photo,
or let's just start again.
So as far as literally just representing
your brand there, I've got a photo I can't
see and a name that I can't pronounce.
Also,
you've done some kind of craziness with
the font up here. I'm not a fan.
It's a little bit try too hard.
And annoyingly,
it might be different on your
phone,
I've got to populate your bio to be able
to see your
call to action.
So for many of you out there, you try
and put too much in your
bios, and it means
that people have to expand.
We call this above the fold.
So in marketing,
when you land on a webpage,
everything you can see is above the
fold,
and it's very important what we put there
because some people are just going
to scroll past it. So straight away,
just with your bio, there's problems.
Because of that,
I'm also going to put a link in the
description to a little mini
course that I've called Your Bio Sucks
and How to Fix It.
It could give you a little bit of an
insight how to do this properly.
Now, there's a lot of red and black. Now,
I'm using dark mode, of course.
Those are the colors of sex and violence.
Typically, men like to pick red
and black because they just think, "Oh,
it kind of
looks cool." I'm not mad on it,
and I'm not mad on how
well-curated all your thumbnails are.
Again, when I see this,
I typically think try hard.
But again,
do not judge a book by its cover.
Let's have a look at the real performance.
So the views are okay.
You're getting about 50% of the total
amount of followers.
And every single thumbnail looks the same
here, which is kind of concerning for me.
I would much rather there be a screen grab
from the video.
And in the video,
let's say you're using a prop.
Sometimes it's quite nice to pick a screen
grab somewhere in the video where it
just looks a bit peculiar,
where you're like, "Oh."
And then people get that little
bit of inquisition.
There's way too much there on a thumbnail.
If that was on YouTube,
you wouldn't put that much text on it.
On YouTube, what do people optimize for?
Like three words on a thumbnail?
A little bit too much.
So I've not even watched a video yet,
and that's some of the
things that I've got an issue with.
[upbeat music] Five seconds into a reel,
nothing's been said.
You're asking me to read,
but I can't even read.
You put white on a background.
That thing at the top,
run more equals win more.
I can't read it.
You could have put a little bit of stroke
on the outside of the
text. But one gripe I have with content
is when people do something like
this. I'm going to guess this
is a pretty short reel.
8, 9, 10, 11. 11 seconds. Cool.
And you put all the
information in the flipping caption.
Now,
if you've gone to the effort of creating a
reel, why put the information in
the caption? If you're going to do that,
just make it a static image and make it
clear to read.
We've kind of got the worst of both sides.
We've just got random football footage
with people just kind of running about.
You've got very difficult stuff to read.
I can't read it at enough pace.
I don't understand why you wouldn't just
do a voiceover on this.
Did you know there was a study that
was done across nine Premier League
seasons,
and it found that winning teams tend to
have more of this one very thing?
And that thing just so happened to be
total running distance.
So when you're looking at your program,
maybe look at the accumulative amount of
running that you're doing,
and for next season,
if you want to test whether or not
this is actually true, whatever it is.
People like being spoken to by people.
I don't understand why you think...
And it would be quicker for you to do
that than it would be to do this because
you've got to type out the caption,
then you've got to set the duration, then
you've got to make sure that one comes in,
then another one comes in after, and
then you've got to match them all up,
and then you've got to find music.
You're making it hard work, bro.
I've watched the video.
I don't know who you are.
I don't know what you're about.
Because people have got something called
idiosyncrasies, which
is kind of like things
that make you unique to you.
And whether that's your approach,
how you talk, your pacing,
all of these things,
I'm getting none of it from that.
Let's try another reel. Oh, God.
Okay, let's try this one. "Warmups
are one of the most underutilized tools I
see
from players.
Start using them to boost your
performance. Check caption." No.
Bro, you want me to read a small book?
Then why isn't this on Twitter?
Why isn't this on Threads?
Why isn't this on LinkedIn?
Why are you using a platform that
is optimized for reels,
communications,
and videos to screenshot a Photoshopped
tweet and then writing a
long caption? Again,
you creating this on Photoshop is
longer than it would take to just talk to
camera. Are you a pussy?
Simply ask.
I'm not asking you to put in more time,
more effort.
I'm asking you to play into the fucking
wind, bro.
If you're a soccer player, right,
and you've got the wind behind you,
you wouldn't
opt, "Oh,
we'll play into the wind," because you're
making things harder than they
are. This is what we need.
But now you're reading off a flipping
teleprompter, so you've obviously got
B-rolls. I've seen you do it before.
When I'm watching this, I'm kind of like,
"Who are you talking to, bro?
Because you're not talking to me." And
if you can't look me in the eyes and say
something,
I don't think you know what you're fucking
on about.
Because if I was to sit here and go,
"If you're someone
that wants to level up on
social media, I think it's imperative
that you were to post
every single..." It just takes away all
credibility.
You've got to look to the camera.
You've got to talk.
Because if you're an expert,
you should be able to just look into
that little dark
lens and just say it as what you're
thinking.
And if you want to read from a
teleprompter or read a script, that
is fine.
But what isn't fine
is not looking at the camera.
Even if I look at the viewfinder in my
FX3, it just kind of puts it off a little
bit. And again, why
is there so much in the caption, bro?
If you have all of this information...
Okay,
this is actually your call to action,
and this should not belong here.
This should belong somewhere else
completely.
This should be on a landing page where we
can make it look nice, and we can put a
VSL,
and we can put a click-through button.
Okay.
"DM me performance to apply for our
next..." Our next intake?
Is it your next intake, singular
or plural?
Because you're making it sound like you've
got a big team here. Let's go.
And you're going to see from this DM,
not even a chatbot set up. Sound.
I could've been ready to fuck, bro.
I could've been ready to buy it.
I'm literally here itching, "Yeah, bro,
give me the soccer plan." And what?
I've got to wait for you to wake up,
wash your cock, check your DMs.
And guess what? Now
that I know it's not an automated bot,
if you get back to me
within the next two hours, I'm like,
"This guy's obviously broke and has got no
clients," because it's now waking up time
in the UK, probably 7:00 a.m.
If you're getting back to me at 7:00 a.m.,
bro, I'm like, "This guy's not busy."
Because when I wake up,
I work with the people that
are paying me the money.
And now, even now, it's 4:20 p.m.,
and I'm getting around to content because
I've
been busy. I'm busy.
I'm a high-paid professional. I'm busy.
But let me tell you this.
Let me tell you something.
If you DM any one of my DM prompts,
you get
Something back straight away.
So there's quite a lot of work, bro.
Quite a lot of work.
Why did this one do so much better?
Let's have a look.
Footballers,
if you want to dominate next season-
Don't know what's up with your audio.
Also, these do nothing, brother.
19 weeks old, I'll let you off.
But hashtags do nothing.
The CEO of Instagram pretty much made
that really clear.
And again,
you're just the geezer sat in a dark room,
so I'm not mad on that.
There's a few things to move on with,
mate. You know what I mean?
Comes from a place of love. What's this?
What's this?
Oh, so you have got a landing page. Cool.
Way too much on it.
Font probably too small as well.
You need a light, bro.
You see this thing here that's making...
I do not look this good in real life.
Let me tell you this,
you bump into me in the street,
you're going to go fucking
hell.
He does not look as good as he looks in
his video because I've got that
fucking light, brother.
I've got a bit of Rembrandt.
You see that little shin on the old delt?
Do you know what that is? A hair light.
What's it doing? Making me look good.
Wish the hair light helped with the hair,
but a baseball cap can do that. Anyway.
If you're a footballer
that can't compete physically-
Still not looking at the camera. Gripe.
But you're using Leadpages,
I'll give you that. Fair play.
Bit of stuff to work on.
Sort this picture out.
If you're really struggling, mate,
we can start a GoFundMe,
and all of us will chip in,
and we'll pay for you to go see a
photographer that's
got a light, and we'll get a photo done.
Also, 68 posts. 68 posts. 68
posts. You've been going since February.
I'll let you off. You look young.
I'll let you off. Moving on. J Leon.
Fitness model.
Fitness, workouts, lifestyle.
Doesn't really do anything, that.
And also, fitness model,
not sure about that. Go back to this. Hmm.
Hmm. Okay.
You're a big dude. Big dude.
jleon@gmail.com.
If you want to make it in life, mate,
think about this. Just get a domain, bro.
Buy the domain jleon.com.
Let's have a little look.
Go daddy. Let's have a little look.
Let's try get a .info, .com.au.
That's because I'm in
Australia.
Even if we got jleon.shop right here, or
jleon.online, that would be a cool one.
Bro, it's $2, it's a £1.
That is not a lot.
And just think how sexy
that would look on your Insta.
Man's got a domain. Because, brother,
have you ever taken a girl
out on a date and maybe she's got,
I don't know, BO,
or she hasn't trimmed her
mustache or something,
and you're thinking, "Come on,
it's the first time we've
ever met. The least you could do
is at least trim
that little mustache you got
going on."
That's what having a Gmail is.
It tells me you're part-time.
It tells me you don't take this seriously.
It tells me that you're going to finish
your flipping game of Fortnite before
getting back to doing the work stuff
that I'm paying you for.
Let's have a little look at this.
30,000 likes, brother.
Dos.
Tres.
Cuatre. Cuatre. Cuatre. Cuatre. Cuatre.
Okay. I was about to contend on that,
but your performance, I'll eat my words.
26,000. 21,000. Brother, I like it.
Do you know what? Fair play.
But let me ask you this,
how many email addresses did you get from
these?
Zero, brother. Zero.
You might have got a few people sliding
into the old DM
saying, "Coach me, bro,"
but you're here flogging hashtags.
But imagine a little call to action on
there.
"If you want to get the same results as
this, comment the word shred." 30,000
likes. 30,000 likes. Now,
why am I not seeing these come up?
Are these carousels as posts?
Because usually, if they're pinned,
they'd be up
here. Hmm, very interesting.
Is this a post?
Either way,
there should've been a call to action on
this.
But good news is,
you've got a bucket here that works.
These posts have shown
that they've worked before.
So you need to do this again,
and put a motherfucking call to action on
it, bro.
Because let me have a look.
My protein discount code. Hmm.
Is that really the most important thing in
your ecosystem, bro?
Because there's a hierarchy here of
importance.
Typically,
when someone says to you what's important
to them, they're actually
saying it in the order of what's important
to them.
So for instance, if they go, "James,
tell me about you." And I go, "Yeah,
I love
cars. I love my dog, and yeah,
I love my family." That says
that I love my
car more than my fucking family. So here,
you're kind of saying, "I like my
protein more than my training plans."
That's what I'm reading, bro.
And My Protein, what are they giving you?
10%? 10%?
How much is that earning you?
Would love to know.
Now, these training plans,
I'm overwhelmed, brother. And guess what?
If I'm here wanting you, bro,
I actually don't want your training plans,
I want a
result. And you've put the results here,
muscle gain, 20-inch arms, abs.
So we need to sell the result to people,
not the very thing.
Because for instance,
when I work with coaches,
link in description, they don't
want to be told off.
They don't want to get roasted.
They actually want to have more clients.
They want to work online.
They want a life of freedom.
They want to do a post or write an email,
go to bed,
and wake up with more money in the bank.
They want... Let me show you yesterday.
If I hold my finger over it.
They want a single email to make
$20,000,
like the one I sent yesterday did.
That's what they want.
Then I sell them the actual process.
So here, rather than training plans,
you could say,
"Do you want to lose weight?
Do you want to build muscle?
Do you want 20-inch arms?" Or better yet,
there should
just be a link here
that talks about the services
that you have.
Hmm, what is this? Because brother, £9.99.
Is that it?
Is that it? Because instead of this...
If you were to hire me,
I would say bun this off. Linktree's dead.
No one's used it in ages,
not since chatbots have actually been
working.
Again, I did a live stream on
that at the weekend
if you want to watch it.
There should be a link here,
not your Linktree, but to J Leon,
jleon.com. On there, "I'm Jay.
I help people lose
fat, build muscle. And actually,
I've got a program
that gets people 20-inch arms.
But have a look at my services down
below." You can either book in a sales
call,
which I don't really like,
or they could just start training with
you.
Someone like you, bro, yoked,
look like you know what you're doing,
I'm sure you're
a nice guy,
you should be charging £55 a week plus for
coaching.
That means that instead of selling six
programs a week passive,
you could just sell
your services.
So there's a few things there I would like
to see.
And also, there's a lot of stuff here.
"Use code J for Impact Wear
and My Protein." If you've worked with me
for three to
six months... Actually, this is an offer.
I'll tell you this.
If you join my mentorship
and this doesn't work within three months,
I'll just
refund you. But if you want to make money,
don't sell something of which you get a
small percentage of.
If you want to make money,
sell your services, bro.
Because 10 people, £50 a week,
£500 a week, then
suddenly, one of your posts explodes,
gets that much before. 30,000 likes.
That's easily a couple of thousand emails.
Going through an email automation,
you bag 15, 20 more clients.
Suddenly, you're earning hundreds,
even thousands more pounds a week and a
month.
That makes a big impact to your business.
No one of your posts is exploding
and getting loads of people to buy clothes
or
fucking My Protein.
People have already got protein, and
if they run out of
protein, they're like, "Oh,
I'll just buy some more." But
when someone's got a
pain,
when someone says they've got twig arms,
when someone says they want to build
muscle, that's where they need help.
They want a service, bro.
And I don't think you have an email list
either.
Someone here say, "Bro, someone
is moving some serious weight."
In the freezer, I'm big as a beetle.
I even now want to see how much the weight
that is, but I can't be fucked.
I'm busy.
I've got other pages to critique.
I'm gone.
Why was there not a preview of what you
were benching, and then maybe something
about it?
Let's say you bench 140 for five.
Then afterwards you're like, "Yo,
what's up?
If you're someone
that wants to bench three plates a side,
here's three tips that
you can implement to improve your bench."
Boom, boom, boom.
"By the way, if you loved that,
I actually put together a free chest
building
program that you can access for free."
Then you give them a link.
"Comment the word chest." They go,
they get the program for free.
They download it, they love it,
they implement it.
They go,
"I've never had a pec pump like it." Then
you follow up and go, "Would you
like to do coaching with me?
It's £55 a week,
and I've got a money-back guarantee.
If the first two weeks you're not really
feeling the difference, I'll refund you in
full." Boom. There is a funnel here
that needs to be happening
Brother. It's just music
and watching you train.
If you had millions of followers,
if you were CBum, I'd allow it.
But you're not.
You're a smaller creator with 10,000.
I just don't think you're monetarily
making the money you need to from the
endorsements and the clothes.
You need to be selling your services,
mate, and your
knowledge and your expertise,
and you need a domain.
Moving on. Sonder So— We
were chatting earlier on in the Discord.
For those of you who don't know,
I work with hundreds of businesses helping
them
with their stuff.
Now I'm pretty sure we're going to change
Sonder Society.
When you say Sonder,
I think of the luxury apartments in JBR at
Rixos. That's what I think
when I see Sonder.
Now,
I think we're going to change your name to
Mary Content.
"I help businesses attract more customers
by turning the work they already do into
reusable content." Delete.
I told you this in the Discord earlier.
I said to you, "Let's change this to,
'I help businesses get seen online.'"
Because then we know what you mean.
And someone goes, "Oh, that's actually...
I do.
I want to get seen online." Whether you're
a plumber, whether you're whatever it
is, you want to get seen online.
That's the whole point, right?
That is the whole point, I'm sure.
So Sonder Society, you could keep that.
You could be like, "Oh,
check out my program." But yeah,
the reason that I know
your face is because we talk all day in
the
Discord. And if I go to any of these,
you'll notice that before I came here to
film, I've been just chirpsing, chatting,
socializing,
actually ripping people's bums down,
offering people new handles for their
stuff. Yeah,
this is where I spend my day before I come
to film. Sonder Society.
Okay, there's quite a bit going on here.
Again, I think we need a VSL up top.
You should know this because you're
already in my program.
A VSL is a video sales letter.
So I would love just up here at the top,
a little
video. You can even hold
that gimbal with your phone and be like,
"I'm
Mary,
and I'm going to use this to capture who
you are and what you do for a
business so more people can decide to use
you." And then this just needs to be
condensed a bit.
When people see paragraphs like this,
they get anxiety, they
want to have a panic attack,
and they get out a brown paper bag
and start
hyperventilating. Bullet points,
typically keep it to three on sales
pages. Don't know, it just works better.
Inquiry,
probably need a stronger call to action
and maybe even
a red button there.
Red buttons typically do better.
Don't mind this as a form.
Don't mind this as a form,
especially in the line of work
that you're in.
But this needs a bit of cleaning up,
needs a video up front.
Because when I land,
if there's a bit too much
and there's a video...
And again,
there are different landing pages for
different people.
Some people come,
just want to watch the video.
they just want to read the text.
Some people come and just buy the product.
So, yeah, bit of work needed. Here you go.
Content shoot, two reels, eight reels,
195. Cool. Eight hours, 800. Nice.
Like to see this. Transparency. Love it.
Looking forward to working with you more
inside.
Let's have a quick look at some of these.
23 posts, 80 followers.
We're not doing terrible.
Some of these are getting some good views.
Let's have a little look here.
[upbeat music] Are you a local business in
Edinburgh or the
Lothians and you want a free content
shoot?
Well,
if you're fed up of never knowing what to
post, I'm giving away-
Don't mind that
It's day one of shooting for Edinburgh TV.
I wouldn't limit yourself to Edinburgh as
well, because if someone starts vibing
with you online,
which hopefully they will,
you should just do UK worldwide.
And if someone's in flipping Truro in
Cornwall, you fly and you
bill the client. You go, "Look, these
are my usual rates.
I need a flight and I need a hotel,
but I'm worth it." So yeah, you should
do UK-wide.
You'll probably get most of your business
in Edinburgh anyway.
One thing I would love to see from you
is what someone was doing before,
then what
you did with them after.
So everyone loves a transformation,
whether it's someone
getting lean, into shape, whatever it is,
I would love to see a before and I'd love
to see an after. This
is this business in Edinburgh.
Before they were doing this, they
were posting static images of their
barbershop.
What I went is I captured the barber in
his element, cutting hair. We did this.
This was a call to action. This
is the benefit you got from it.
If you would like me to do this for your
business...
So even like simply if you were a tiler,
I would say, "Right, show me the bathroom
before, show me the bathroom after."
If you're a landscaper,
"Show me the fucking
garden before,
show me the garden after."
If you're a B2B coach, "Show me the
revenue before,
show me the revenue after." People love a
before and after.
Again, there's a link in the description.
If not, and you want to get roasted,
link in the description.
It's a common theme.
Okay, Will Smythe. Will Smythe.
Nequals 1 Will
Smythe. What? Brother, were you drunk?
Were you drunk picking that?
N
equals 1. Is that what you're saying?
No one knows what that means, brother.
No one knows what that means.
And the people that do know what
that means ain't
paying you. Will S— change it, too much.
This display picture,
I've got a hair light of your oiled-up
rig on a photo shoot.
I can't even see your face.
You're in the dark.
It's nonce vibes, brother.
For those of you not in the UK,
nonce means pedo.
It's pedo-ish.
You look like someone hiding in the
shadows about to sexually
assault someone. Come on.
And this just shows me, again, hierarchy,
that all you
care about is your abs.
And let me tell you this,
in the fitness industry, let me
tell you something. Right now,
I've got abs in your DP,
abs in your pin pic.
I can tell straight away all you care
about is having a six-pack.
Now,
the people that you want to work with may
not be as shallow as
you. I'm sorry, but that's it.
They've got real problems.
They want to do things.
They want to perform.
Represent your brand, not with your body,
because guess what?
No one's hiring a fucking body unless
you're a body double or unless you're a
fucking stuntman. They want you.
They want the intellectual property, the
knowledge, the experience,
not your fucking abs.
You're trying to do it as an appeal to
authority,
but you know what would be a good
appeal to authority? Fucking helping me.
And every time I land on your page, going,
"Fucking hell, never thought of that."
So that's, I'm sorry,
but that's just a bit shit straight away
up here.
"I help you train
and eat like a real everyday athlete."
Now, everyday athlete has
been rinsed by the fitness industry.
What does that mean? What does that mean?
Let's imagine I'm your perfect client.
I don't know what that means.
Crush HYROX, CrossFit, or life. Faster
and stronger in eight weeks or money back
guaranteed. Everyday athletes. Again,
if you were to just say, "I help
normal people get exceptional results in
CrossFit and HYROX," cool.
Trying a bit hard there, mate.
It doesn't look like you revised that.
Let me tell you this.
When we're on YouTube and we have a title,
we'll do
10 titles, 10 more titles, 20 more titles.
We'll stare at a title for an hour until
we get the perfect title.
This is the title to your brand,
and I just don't think you've thought this
through. "I help you train and eat..."
And there's no call to action to these
links. Are these links important?
Facebook profile.
Why would you send someone from socials to
socials? There's a funnel, brother.
Social media, contact information,
or data, email marketing, landing
page, sale.
You're just sending people side to side.
Find what works.
What is that as a call to action?
I don't know. Find what works. Again, abs.
All you care about, bro,
is how lean you are.
And the issue is, I'm worried that
if I hire you,
that you might care more about
you than you care about me. And
if I get those vibes,
I'll hire someone else.
N=1s, bruv.
Do you know how many dyslexic people
are just going to be calling you
Neckwells? Oh yeah,
I worked with this Neckwells. Neckwells?
Neckwells One, actually. Nutrition
and training programs,
be your own experiment, a
journal of self.
Why have you got links to your social
media here, bro?
We spoke about the funnel before.
You've just taken them,
you've just fucking
impressed them enough to leave social
media, and you're sending them back.
It's like chatting up a girl at the bar,
leaving the bar with her, and going,
"Should we go back inside?" She's going to
be like, "All right.
I thought we were going back to yours,
but fine." What's going on there?
Subscribe to N Equals. Subscribe to what?
Exclusive email updates.
No one wants exclusive email updates.
You need a lead magnet, bro.
And you're fucking back here again,
sending people back to your fucking
socials.
What are you doing? People
are just going to be bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing.
Because guess what? This
is what's going to happen, mate.
They're going to click on YouTube.
They're going to get over here.
They're going to see you haven't posted in
fucking six months, which just shows me
you're disorganized. Shock.
Your rig in the first picture.
I'm now here going, "Oh,
this guy doesn't even fucking use his
fucking thing." Oh,
how to ride the devil bike. Thrilling.
Then I'm going to go click here,
and then I'm going to look at a load of
YouTube
videos that are really fucking
interesting, and before you know it,
I'm here
watching something else.
I'm watching a fucking car vs. drag race.
And this is your fault because you sent me
to YouTube.
Hey, bro,
if you're fucking chatting to
that girl and you're leaving the bar with
her,
do not send her into another bar full of
male models, because suddenly you do
not look as attractive,
and that's what's going to happen.
So I've not even looked at your content
yet, mate.
This all up here is fucked. It's fucked.
That's why you've done 1,000 posts
and only got 2,000 followers.
I tell you that.
And no one's using this.
There's no call to action.
There's nothing appealing.
There's no reason here why I should do
anything with that.
Good news is it can change.
You've posted a testimonial here, which
is fine.
No one cares. Just going to throw
that out there. No one cares. They don't.
23 people do, but no one really does.
If you're taking people's funnel again,
social media, good lead magnet, give
someone something that they want. Sweet.
Then you were to email them
and with more value,
then you could just email them out
of the blue. Remember that 20K email I
was showing off about?
And you could say, "Hey, by the way,
here's Ben.
Been working with him." You could have
made this a big emotional thing.
Again, hashtags don't do anything.
31 weeks old.
23 likes in 31 week. All right, fine.
[singing] Had to count stacks. Knew
that ass was real.
When I hit, it bounce back.
You ain't getting checks.
Work, work, shoot
Brother,
surely you spend time on social media.
You just nodding at someone
and putting a bit of text there.
It's shit.
It's fucking low effort.
I don't know who you are yet, N=1
or Neckwells,
you could just walked in and gone, "Hey,
I'm Neckwells.
I'm going to fix your hang power snatch."
Bro, if you're helping out everyday
athletes,
which I don't even know what an everyday
athlete is, do they know what
hang power snatch is? Maybe.
They might have done a few in their
CrossFit session.
But again,
these people doing hang power snatches in
CrossFit don't even know that
they're not doing it right.
They don't even know they're bouncing.
And again, out of all the people
that I met in CrossFit doing CrossFit
before
jujitsu, none of them were like,
"I just started training here because I
wanted to
fix my hang power snatch." So-
[singing] Bam, bam, bam, bam, di-dum, bam,
bam, bam.
Ay, watch how
No talking, improve core engagement,
shoulder stability. Cool. Boring.
[singing] Work it, make it, do it.
Makes it harder. Better, best.
You just shared with us your workout.
Social media, your job
is to solve a problem.
Right? It's to solve a problem.
You're not solving any problems here. Why?
No one's vibing with your content.
And no one's vibing with your content,
that's why you don't really care about all
the other stuff that's going on there.
There's so much to fix here.
Who woke up today going, "Fuck,
I'd just love to see a WOD." I'd just love
to
see a WOD. Four people in three days,
apparently.
And even then, I'm sorry to say this,
brother,
if we were to look at these likes,
I'd say another HYROX athlete
or CrossFitter by the looks of it.
Fitness, Sophie J, could be your missus
or someone that fancies you.
Or Gemma could be... I don't know.
But even, I'd say 50% of those likes
are just
sympathy likes. Oh,
there's Neckwells getting into a workout.
I'll give him a little double tap.
They didn't watch it.
They definitely didn't watch it
or do anything really with it,
otherwise it
wouldn't have gotten shown to 24 people.
If I'm going to spend this long on your
profile, bro, I should really know who you
are. Let's go ChatGPT.
Didn't Phil Learning have a book called
"N=1?" In most
contexts, N=1 means a sample size of one.
Mate, give up on this branding. Right?
Your name's Will Smythe.
Just You're Will. All right?
Any clients you've ever had, You're Will.
We spent way too long on You're Will
there, but come on, easy fixes.
Easy fixes. This in your world
is someone coming to you that's just a
fucking
mad athlete that's good at everything
that just has got bad technique.
If you just fix your technique,
you'll be laughing. You will.
Tina Carter Pilates.
Don't mind this. 4,000 followers,
700 posts. You're getting at it. Oh,
here we go.
500 gentle Pilates classes. I like this.
Virtual Pilates classes.
I like it. I like it.
Sign up to seven days free trial.
I like it.
Few bits going on here, right?
If you have a link to something,
just send the link,
because if they do the seven-day free
trial, aren't you going to get their email
anyway?
If you're going to get their email from
the trial, just push the trial, and
don't send them to Facebook.
Just have a link to where you want them to
go.
Wherever you send someone to,
like for instance,
when you do your web form to apply
for the roast,
I'm doing it for your email address.
And then I'm probably going to shower you
with nice little offers.
I'm going to let you know
if there's a discount or an event
or something to come
to.
There's no way you're getting into my
ecosystem without, one, me giving you
something you want, and two,
without getting your email address.
You know this studio, these vibes,
I'm liking it. I'm liking it.
Profile picture, liking it. Okay,
why did this one do so well? Hmm.
Pinned post,
you're just showing off your pricing.
That's all right.
One month, $10.99. Oh, so six months,
55 pounds.
Six months, 55 pounds, it's not bad.
And do I get what?
Like daily workouts with that?
It's pretty good.
You strike me as someone
that might have a soft voice.
Do you know what?
I want to hear it. If you're someone
that experiences hip pain,
then why not try
adding this to your Pilates regimen?
This Pilates move lengthens, strengthens,
and transforms your core like nothing
else.
Let's just get a bit of talking in this,
get a bit of personality in here.
Let's get rid of the hashtags.
Let's do less in the caption.
Give me it in the video.
I want you guys to put everything into the
video so
that at the end of the video,
they're like they've got everything.
Not, "Oh, where's the rest? Oh,
it's in the caption. Oh, I've got to read.
Oh, am I on fucking..." What's it called?
Substack.
Have you ever heard of the bow pose?
This is me doing it here.
Although this is quite difficult to start
doing, once you can do it, it's a great
way for opening up your tight hips.
For any of you that spend long days
sitting, this is the perfect accompanying
exercise that you could do in the privacy
of your own home to not only feel better,
but alleviate sore joints.
If you wanted to do these with me every
day,
I've got memberships from eight pounds a
month. You know what I mean?
Let's sell a bit more. This studio
is Leng, as they call it in the UK.
Leng, look at that lighting,
the warehouse vibes, the
rustic-ness. I'm loving it.
You've got the recipe here for so much,
Tina.
I just want to see it a little bit better
used.
And I want you to start selling to people.
I want you to start getting some offers.
I want you to start saying in this,
the only thing I want your caption to say
is,
"Do a month of Pilates with me for free.
Comment the word Pilates." Then you bring
them in, you give them the first month
for free,
you start billing from the second month,
you offer a money-back
guarantee.
Let's start getting people into the
ecosystem.
You've got 4,000 followers.
If you just communicate a little bit more
with this,
you'll be flying. Next, J. Bush Fitness.
Hate your photo.
Hate it. First of all,
the camera's at a low level looking up,
so you're quite
literally looking down on us. The rig,
it's all right. It's all right.
Is that really going to be enough to have
an appeal to
authority? I wouldn't, bro.
I'm invested a lot.
I'm fairly jacked,
and I don't even do this, bro.
I go sleeves on for a lot of stuff.
The only reason I've done this
is I come from
training. Rock bottom discipline
and growth, helping you master fitness,
mental
health. I don't really know what you do.
Don't really know what you do.
Fitness, you're just a fitness guy.
Don't like this, bruv.
I'm going to throw it out there.
You're not big enough for this, okay?
If you're on your own personal journey,
nah, come on, bro, this ain't it.
This ain't it.
Or even though this video could be pretty
good, you've
absolutely killed it with that.
Like the homoerotic stuff.
Nah, bro.
You're just another person. All right.
Let me tell you a little cheat code,
right?
If you're a personal trainer
and you want to do well as a personal
trainer, don't
be a classic personal trainer bellend,
which I'm afraid you
are doing here. Your job
is not to be jacked.
Your job is not to show off your muscles.
Your job is not to show us your workouts.
Your fucking job is to help people with
the problems that they face on a
daily basis.
And if you can help them with those
problems online, they will
hire you.
But if you make this all about you,
you're just looking at other fitness
bellends and taking advice from them.
They're all broke. They all have no money.
They all live at home with their parents.
And you will get in the same fucking trap
if you do not
realize that everything you do
is about solving people's problems
online. And it just doesn't look to me.
"What I ate in a day.
Microwave only." Look at this. Bro,
I'm sorry to say it,
you look like a fucking self-obsessed,
narcissistic cunt.
That is the last thing that people
are going to hire. Fix this. Stop this.
Put your fucking shirt on.
Start solving problems, right?
I don't know if you've got any clients.
If you do have any clients,
write a fucking list of the 10 biggest
problems they
face. Go solve them, because guess what?
Sandra in the gym feels sorry for you,
and you're helping her get rid of her
bingo
wings and drop 15 pounds before she goes
to Benidorm next door.
There's fucking a few Sandras out there
that could hire you.
You should be getting content working with
your clients, showcasing what your
clients are doing. "Hey, today,
I've got Sandra doing a rift elevated
split squat
at a deficit,
but we decided to drop the weight
and add the deficit so she'd get a
larger range of motion.
You should try this at home. She loves it.
She doesn't like to wear a bone too much.
This is an exercise
that works for my clients." Too
self-obsessed, mate, and no
call to action. TikTok.
You think someone's going to go, "Okay,
jbush.fitness.
Let's go to TikTok, jbush.fit."? Stupid.
Get a link in there, offer something.
There is nothing going on here. This
is not good enough.
You will not survive with this level of
content. Anay Coach.
Oh, fuck. Have I picked a foreign person?
Maribor, Slova- are you Turkish
or something?
And you do them all the way down. This
is because-
Why is this in one language
and this in another?
The pull-up reps drop by half.
And for the third exercise-
Third exercise? Third exercise?
Where's the others?
Oh,
you can't have these as separate reels,
brother, because not everyone watching
this has seen the ones before.
Get rid of the hashtags.
They look desperate.
Again, don't need to put this.
If your video has it in,
don't need to put this in
there.
"And for the third exercise," shit hook.
Shit hook.
If you're someone that's struggling to do
chin-ups, if you're someone that can't do
a chin-up,
if you're someone that's never done 10
chin-ups in a row, if you're
looking to get better at chin-ups,
these are hooks.
Then there are other things
that we can make, like statements.
You're doing chin-ups wrong.
You're doing chin-ups ineffectively.
You're making chin-ups harder than they
need to be. You're whatever it is.
That's not it. And show me.
You've got a fucking bar.
You're in the forest.
You look like a jacked guy.
If you're good at chin-ups,
if you want to appeal to
authority, do it.
You could even green screen yourself doing
chin-ups.
This is me repping out 25 chin-ups.
I wasn't always able to do 25 chin-ups,
but if you just follow these three
training
principles,
you could be able to do this as well.
Call to action.
"Want more pull-up tips?
Check #anaycoach." No, brother. What?
I'm going to click that
and see your posts. No, bruv.
I've clicked your hashtag.
Look what it's given me.
Your call to action smells terrible, mate.
Smelly, smelly, smelly.
Is this where you want to send people?
Have you even checked this? Doubt it.
Needs a lot of work, bro.
Not going to lie to you.
No call to action.
The only thing that I can click here
is fucking Facebook. Not good enough.
Jack DoorLifts. That photo got to go.
Again, everyone,
please do not be fucking bellends.
You look like a bellend there, mate.
You know it. I know it.
You've got those rings inside the rings.
Don't know what you're doing there.
You're using that weird font here.
Don't like it. Using this weird font here.
Don't like it. "DM me. Calendly.
Book in a call." How many of these are you
getting? Not many, I bet.
Let's have a look.
I can see the way
that you kind of only opened your diary
for a few hours,
make it look like you're busier than you
really are. I'll rate that hustle.
That's one thing that I would say
is pretty good that you're doing.
Conscious Physique Coach. What does
that mean? What does that mean?
What does that mean? I don't know.
"DM intention free toolkit.
DM transform one-to-one coaching." Mate,
you should really just be trying to get
emails, so I'd give you that tool. What
is a toolkit? What is a toolkit, brother?
I don't know.
"DM for a free toolkit." For what?
What's the outcome?
What are you promising? I don't know,
brother. That needs a lot of work.
Come on, come on. All right.
Remember what I said, okay?
I'm going to point to all the things
that makes you a bellend. That.
Okay, not actually too many.
I'll let you off.
Views are a bit smelly,
but let's go through some of your reels,
see what we got.
Discipline, presence, flow.
No hook.
80 kilos bench press for 10 reps.
Statement, no curiosity.
12 years for techniques like that,
give up.
[music] Audio only in one ear. Oh,
actually, no, that's the song.
Bruv, don't do this. Don't do this.
You are pushing people away.
That's a bellend thing. No hook.
People telling me my bars just random.
Too good.
Bored.
Is it possible to get cellulite on your
abs?
Do men even get cellulite?
Wow.
Don't know what's going on. Shit caption.
Hashtags don't do anything, bruv.
Come on.
He looks fit. I would-
Weird. I'm gone.
I'm never coming back to your page again.
That is not how people should feel
when they come here.
This page is supposed to be representing a
business.
You are supposed to be a brand
that you are representing
and standing up for.
This just does not do it for me.
It's not good enough. And last one,
Pete BJJ.
Okay, let's have a look.
Jiu-jitsu brown belt. All right.
So putting your brown belt around your
head is your appeal to authority.
I get it.
All right. You're a brown belt.
That's cool.
Trying to get people to go to your
YouTube. Let me tell you this, brother.
Rather than putting your YouTube here as a
call to action, I'm not sure if this is
a business or just a hobby, there
are billions of people on YouTube
already. If you want them,
just make good content.
Hey, you got a few here,
some stuff coming through here.
Work on your titles a bit. Your titles
are a little bit too long.
Not much curiosity built.
And looks like you're just sharing shorts
here.
So if you're just sharing shorts on
YouTube and you're just sharing shorts, of
course, tongue twister, on Instagram,
I just don't understand the point of that.
Now,
you're using this thumbnail all the time.
No offense, mate.
If I was to say to you,
you've never met you, you don't know you,
and I was...
All right,
let me say I just grab some random people
and I get them to go and tie a
brown belt around their head.
You'd say that person's a fucking bellend.
It is how you're coming across.
Let's have a little look.
Okay, if you're going to show a kneebar,
why slap the camera first?
You know what I mean?
Kneebar time here.
Good vocals. I like that.
Chance to go down
and train at London Grapple with my mate
Zach.
I know Zach. Anyway.
Look at him hit this lovely little
transition into a
kneebar. And we're go-
I wish more people knew
that belts mean nothing.
BJJ matches so you don't have to part-
I'm not sure about the belt around the
head, mate. I'm just not.
Hashtags don't do anything.
I'm not really sure what you're doing with
this, if I'm
honest. I would love to know more,
but I just don't know what you're doing.
You've put your profile forward because
you want to get better and you want some
feedback, but the issue
is I can't tell you what to do better
because I don't know
what it is you do or what you're doing.
Because I've arrived on your page,
I just have no idea.
But stop putting your belt on your head.
That's what I'd say for a start.
Okay, so that wraps up.
If you made it this far in the roast,
make sure you put
your name in. Get a roast yourself.
If not, all the paid and free things
are in the description.
And if you still stay around
and you're not interested in any of those,
YouTube's a
smart bugger and it's recommended
that you watch this here.
So I'd go ahead and click this,
and we can start a binge session where you
just
watch all of my videos,
and the likeliness of you doing business
with me increases.
But don't worry.
Even though you're going to give me loads
of money, I'm going to
help you make more back.
Goodbye.